menshairstylesnow.com 2019-02-02

# Privacy Policy | Men's Haircuts + Hairstyles 2019

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.

At [MensHairstylesNow.com](https://www.menshairstylesnow.com/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy outlines the types of personal information received and collected by MensHairstylesNow.com, and how that information is used.

 **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, MensHairstylesNow.com makes use of log files. The information within log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, ISP data, date and time stamps, and website analytics used to analyze trends. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies and Web Beacons**

MensHairstylesNow.com does not use cookies, but our third-party advertisers do.

 **DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.MensHairstylesNow.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.MensHairstylesNow.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting Google’s privacy policy at http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense and Amazon.com. MHN is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and linking to Amazon.

These third-party ad servers and ad networks use this technology and information to serve the most relevant advertisements on MensHairstylesNow.com. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

MensHairstylesNow.com has no access to or control over the cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. MensHairstylesNow.com’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites or check out this link – http://optout.networkadvertising.org/#!/.
